(Penny:)Okay, sweetie, I know you think
you're explaining yourself...
(Penny:)...but you're really not.
(Sheldon:)Just come with me.
[ON STEREO]
Tell me have you ever really
Really, really ever loved a woman?
(Sheldon:)Well?
- Well, what?
- What does it mean?
(Penny:)Come on, you went to college.
Yes, but I was 11.
(Penny:)A tie on the doorknob usually means
someone doesn't wanna be disturbed...
(Penny:)...because they're, you know,
getting busy.
(Sheldon:)So you're saying
Leonard has a girl in there?
(Penny:)Well, either that or he's lost his tie rack
and gotten really into Bryan Adams.
LESLIE [FLATLY]:
Oh, Leonard, you magnificent beast.
(Penny:)We really shouldn't be standing here.
(Sheldon(entering living room):)This is very awkward.
(Penny:)Oh, come on. You know,
Leonard's had girls over before, right?